I am currently on 160 milligrams a week
um injections twice of cpon 8 and I the
nandrolone for joint pain how much
should I adjust my te with adding in
nandrolone that's I mean it's impossible
to tell on here uh because everybody's
different I would start by not changing
anything other than adding nandrolone
like that's what I did when I started
taking low do nerone for joint pain I
didn't touch my trt dose at first
because why would you change two
variables at once instead of one so add
the nandrolone first to see how you
tolerate it start low I I mean seriously
50 milligrams a week is usually plenty
for for joint pain relief 50 to 80
something like that 50 to 100 wouldn't
jump up to 200 milligrams a week in
nandrolone uh I wouldn't even start at
100 I would it's got such a long
halflife start at 50 milligrams a week
for six weeks and then see how you feel
and if your joint pain gets better but
you still feel great don't adjust your
tea dose like that that's it just one
variable at a time and be patient I
think that's the key with most of this
stuff